[{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88bc8"},"rt":18241,"condition":"11111","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":83090,"subject":"K8XWF","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44448","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88bc9"},"rt":11299,"condition":"11111","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":94612,"subject":"K8XWF","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44448","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"A A D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88bca"},"rt":13276,"condition":"11111","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":108135,"subject":"K8XWF","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44448","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88bcb"},"rt":45968,"condition":"11111","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":154320,"subject":"K8XWF","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44448","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88bcc"},"rt":100866,"condition":"11111","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":255454,"subject":"K8XWF","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44448","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88bce"},"rt":10609,"condition":"11111","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":270328,"subject":"K8XWF","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44448","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88bcf"},"rt":23939,"condition":"11111","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":294563,"subject":"K8XWF","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44448","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88bd0"},"rt":33523,"condition":"11111","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":328299,"subject":"K8XWF","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44448","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":"E I I I J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88bd1"},"rt":16965,"condition":"11111","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":345515,"subject":"K8XWF","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44448","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88bd2"},"rt":22553,"condition":"11111","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":368288,"subject":"K8XWF","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44448","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88bd3"},"rt":7304,"condition":"11111","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":375813,"subject":"K8XWF","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44448","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88bd4"},"rt":4850,"condition":"11111","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":380880,"subject":"K8XWF","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44448","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88bd5"},"rt":16635,"condition":"11111","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":397909,"subject":"K8XWF","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44448","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88bd6"},"rt":16974,"condition":"11111","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":415100,"subject":"K8XWF","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44448","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88bd7"},"rt":23908,"condition":"11111","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":439222,"subject":"K8XWF","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44448","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88be9"},"rt":29003,"condition":"11111","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":111783,"subject":"GCW1R","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44449","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":"1A A F F C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88bea"},"rt":24339,"condition":"11111","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":136219,"subject":"GCW1R","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44449","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"O Z E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88beb"},"rt":18163,"condition":"11111","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":154481,"subject":"GCW1R","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44449","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88bec"},"rt":23500,"condition":"11111","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":178076,"subject":"GCW1R","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44449","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"U H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88bed"},"rt":32545,"condition":"11111","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":210719,"subject":"GCW1R","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44449","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"O I I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88bef"},"rt":19794,"condition":"11111","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":233904,"subject":"GCW1R","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44449","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E E 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88bf0"},"rt":25700,"condition":"11111","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":259697,"subject":"GCW1R","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44449","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88bf1"},"rt":57542,"condition":"11111","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":317321,"subject":"GCW1R","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44449","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"B C C B X X X X X X O F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88bf2"},"rt":14509,"condition":"11111","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":331943,"subject":"GCW1R","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44449","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88bf3"},"rt":48501,"condition":"11111","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":380537,"subject":"GCW1R","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44449","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"F F F N O X F F F F J B B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88bf4"},"rt":6818,"condition":"11111","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":387493,"subject":"GCW1R","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44449","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88bf5"},"rt":9364,"condition":"11111","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":396946,"subject":"GCW1R","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44449","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88bf6"},"rt":29972,"condition":"11111","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":427010,"subject":"GCW1R","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44449","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"Z O C C O O H O O C G G F F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88bf7"},"rt":24070,"condition":"11111","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":451175,"subject":"GCW1R","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44449","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88bf8"},"rt":34091,"condition":"11111","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":485356,"subject":"GCW1R","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44449","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"E F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c09"},"rt":127302,"condition":"11111","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":197907,"subject":"0BBET","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41013","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"A A C C 008 AMC C C C C C C C C 312 PM01 PM02 PM01 PM10 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM04 PM01 PM12 PM10 AM09 AM08 AM08 PM11 AMF 02 PM12 PM01 PMF F 02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AMF D K Z F 11 AMF F 02 PM11 AMC 11 AM10 AMA A A F Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c0a"},"rt":21118,"condition":"11111","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":219311,"subject":"0BBET","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41013","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c0b"},"rt":30035,"condition":"11111","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":249449,"subject":"0BBET","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41013","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C C C F F C 08 AM09 AM09 AM10 AM10 AM08 AM08 AM09 AM10 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM12 PM11 AM10 AMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c0c"},"rt":9638,"condition":"11111","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":259183,"subject":"0BBET","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41013","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c0d"},"rt":28454,"condition":"11111","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":287738,"subject":"0BBET","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41013","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"08 AMI I O C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c0f"},"rt":16834,"condition":"11111","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":311301,"subject":"0BBET","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41013","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c10"},"rt":25698,"condition":"11111","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":337133,"subject":"0BBET","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41013","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"01 PMO H O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c11"},"rt":56644,"condition":"11111","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":393880,"subject":"0BBET","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41013","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"C B B B 11 AM12 PMI G E 02 PMM X X J B 10 AMG C O 02 PMO C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c12"},"rt":51552,"condition":"11111","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":445531,"subject":"0BBET","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41013","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"M M 09 AME F F 02 PM01 PM12 PMI E E E F B B B B F J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c13"},"rt":13078,"condition":"11111","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":458710,"subject":"0BBET","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41013","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c14"},"rt":11490,"condition":"11111","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":470301,"subject":"0BBET","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41013","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"12 PM12 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c15"},"rt":7181,"condition":"11111","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":477584,"subject":"0BBET","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41013","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c16"},"rt":11553,"condition":"11111","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":489238,"subject":"0BBET","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41013","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c17"},"rt":12510,"condition":"11111","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":501855,"subject":"0BBET","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41013","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c18"},"rt":13339,"condition":"11111","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":515292,"subject":"0BBET","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41013","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"11 AM12 PM02 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c2a"},"rt":35758,"condition":"11111","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":86146,"subject":"SA81V","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34827","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"011 AM11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c2b"},"rt":10869,"condition":"11111","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":97078,"subject":"SA81V","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34827","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"Z D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c2c"},"rt":40795,"condition":"11111","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":137941,"subject":"SA81V","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34827","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c2d"},"rt":12188,"condition":"11111","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":150193,"subject":"SA81V","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34827","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c2e"},"rt":121526,"condition":"11111","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":271789,"subject":"SA81V","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34827","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c30"},"rt":9249,"condition":"11111","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":284057,"subject":"SA81V","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34827","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c31"},"rt":12064,"condition":"11111","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":296188,"subject":"SA81V","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34827","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c32"},"rt":45278,"condition":"11111","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":341536,"subject":"SA81V","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34827","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E E 11 AM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c33"},"rt":21627,"condition":"11111","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":363219,"subject":"SA81V","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34827","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c34"},"rt":36452,"condition":"11111","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":399734,"subject":"SA81V","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34827","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c35"},"rt":13788,"condition":"11111","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":413586,"subject":"SA81V","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34827","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c36"},"rt":12850,"condition":"11111","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":426500,"subject":"SA81V","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34827","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c37"},"rt":23877,"condition":"11111","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":450433,"subject":"SA81V","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34827","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c38"},"rt":19101,"condition":"11111","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":469600,"subject":"SA81V","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34827","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c39"},"rt":74431,"condition":"11111","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":544097,"subject":"SA81V","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34827","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c4b"},"rt":97480,"condition":"11111","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":143175,"subject":"WTEFO","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41886","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM10 AM11 AM11 AMA A 10 AM11 AMF 11 AMF 11 AM11 AM11 AMA Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c4c"},"rt":61777,"condition":"11111","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":205230,"subject":"WTEFO","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41886","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":"04 PM03 PM03 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM08 AM09 AM02 PM03 PM09 AM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c4d"},"rt":71719,"condition":"11111","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":277241,"subject":"WTEFO","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41886","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c4e"},"rt":76151,"condition":"11111","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":353664,"subject":"WTEFO","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41886","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"04 PM04 PM04 PMU U 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c4f"},"rt":53967,"condition":"11111","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":407917,"subject":"WTEFO","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41886","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c51"},"rt":13585,"condition":"11111","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":428125,"subject":"WTEFO","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41886","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c52"},"rt":225519,"condition":"11111","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":653752,"subject":"WTEFO","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41886","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":"C H F O J O O F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c53"},"rt":87005,"condition":"11111","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":741023,"subject":"WTEFO","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41886","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"C C E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c54"},"rt":14915,"condition":"11111","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":756202,"subject":"WTEFO","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41886","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"01 PM01 PMI "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c55"},"rt":71007,"condition":"11111","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":827316,"subject":"WTEFO","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41886","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c56"},"rt":9934,"condition":"11111","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":837528,"subject":"WTEFO","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41886","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c57"},"rt":7579,"condition":"11111","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":845215,"subject":"WTEFO","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41886","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c58"},"rt":53942,"condition":"11111","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":899259,"subject":"WTEFO","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41886","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c59"},"rt":91632,"condition":"11111","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":990994,"subject":"WTEFO","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41886","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c5a"},"rt":4525,"condition":"11111","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":995780,"subject":"WTEFO","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41886","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G,H,Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c6b"},"rt":97026,"condition":"11111","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":317192,"subject":"N4FXV","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36705","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,C,F","hovered":"809 AM11 AM11 AM11 AMA A A A A A 08 AM12 PM11 AM11 AMA 01 PM12 PMF F 01 PM211 AMA A 10 AM11 AM11 AMU D D 11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c6c"},"rt":62791,"condition":"11111","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":380537,"subject":"N4FXV","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36705","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,D,E","hovered":"2C U 02 PM01 PM12 PMZ D D D Z 12 PMD 08 PM08 PM12 PM01 PME E E 04 PMG E E D D D D J H H 09 AM10 AME E K K 12 PMU E G 03 PM04 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c6d"},"rt":130081,"condition":"11111","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":511326,"subject":"N4FXV","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36705","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X,D","hovered":"11 AM12 PM02 PM11 AM10 AM10 AM10 AMC 11 AM11 AMC C C C 4A 09 AMC C 09 AM10 AMC 10 AM11 AM12 PM07 PM08 PM07 PM08 PM07 PM06 PM05 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM12 PM11 AM03 PM12 PM261008 PMC B 08 PMD D D D 7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c6e"},"rt":42596,"condition":"11111","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":554602,"subject":"N4FXV","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36705","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E,B","hovered":"05 PM102 PMB 04 PMB 04 PM04 PME E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c6f"},"rt":7564,"condition":"11111","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":562563,"subject":"N4FXV","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36705","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c71"},"rt":108083,"condition":"11111","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":675608,"subject":"N4FXV","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36705","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.3333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":4,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F,K,Z,X","hovered":"E G 08 AMI 08 AM09 AM08 AM11 AM10 AM08 AM08 AM09 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM01 PM12 PMB J 08 AME 08 AM09 AM209 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PMX O O X X X O 02 PMZ 10 AM11 AM12 PM02 PM02 PM02 PM11 AMF 03 PM02 PM02 PM02 PM02 PM02 PM02 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c72"},"rt":74868,"condition":"11111","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":751247,"subject":"N4FXV","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36705","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.25,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J,N,O","hovered":"4F F I I C C 04 PMO C C C C O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c73"},"rt":2064,"condition":"11111","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":754421,"subject":"N4FXV","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36705","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c74"},"rt":1318,"condition":"11111","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":755920,"subject":"N4FXV","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36705","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c75"},"rt":931,"condition":"11111","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":756963,"subject":"N4FXV","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36705","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c76"},"rt":891,"condition":"11111","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":757961,"subject":"N4FXV","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36705","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c77"},"rt":1768,"condition":"11111","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":760075,"subject":"N4FXV","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36705","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c78"},"rt":3620,"condition":"11111","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":763806,"subject":"N4FXV","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36705","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c79"},"rt":1392,"condition":"11111","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":766069,"subject":"N4FXV","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36705","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c7a"},"rt":1318,"condition":"11111","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":767694,"subject":"N4FXV","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36705","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c8c"},"rt":26363,"condition":"11111","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":90238,"subject":"45DKK","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42121","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"2A 2A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c8d"},"rt":12296,"condition":"11111","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":102637,"subject":"45DKK","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42121","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F O O E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c8e"},"rt":28819,"condition":"11111","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":131553,"subject":"45DKK","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42121","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"A A C J X 08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c8f"},"rt":11238,"condition":"11111","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":142903,"subject":"45DKK","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42121","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"C Z 01 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c90"},"rt":19260,"condition":"11111","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":162270,"subject":"45DKK","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42121","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c92"},"rt":20727,"condition":"11111","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":187091,"subject":"45DKK","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42121","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"J 09 AM08 AM09 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c93"},"rt":23893,"condition":"11111","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":211171,"subject":"45DKK","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42121","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":"2O M 12 PMM F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c94"},"rt":70578,"condition":"11111","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":281854,"subject":"45DKK","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42121","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B B B B B X X G F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c95"},"rt":82300,"condition":"11111","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":364470,"subject":"45DKK","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42121","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,K","hovered":"B J E J J J I 1B A A F J 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c96"},"rt":13100,"condition":"11111","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":377903,"subject":"45DKK","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42121","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"H 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c97"},"rt":12170,"condition":"11111","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":390186,"subject":"45DKK","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42121","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c98"},"rt":7651,"condition":"11111","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":398017,"subject":"45DKK","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42121","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c99"},"rt":13185,"condition":"11111","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":411303,"subject":"45DKK","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42121","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"O H Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c9a"},"rt":13367,"condition":"11111","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":424769,"subject":"45DKK","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42121","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"01 PM02 PM02 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88c9b"},"rt":22403,"condition":"11111","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":447271,"subject":"45DKK","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42121","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cad"},"rt":31100,"condition":"11111","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":100796,"subject":"ZQ9M2","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43582","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cae"},"rt":29114,"condition":"11111","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":130021,"subject":"ZQ9M2","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43582","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"O H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88caf"},"rt":32632,"condition":"11111","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":162759,"subject":"ZQ9M2","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43582","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cb0"},"rt":26807,"condition":"11111","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":189846,"subject":"ZQ9M2","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43582","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cb1"},"rt":37199,"condition":"11111","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":227151,"subject":"ZQ9M2","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43582","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"612 PM01 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cb3"},"rt":8857,"condition":"11111","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":241582,"subject":"ZQ9M2","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43582","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cb4"},"rt":16325,"condition":"11111","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":258049,"subject":"ZQ9M2","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43582","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cb5"},"rt":31019,"condition":"11111","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":289173,"subject":"ZQ9M2","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43582","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"6X J B X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cb6"},"rt":20352,"condition":"11111","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":309636,"subject":"ZQ9M2","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43582","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"H A B B J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cb7"},"rt":27266,"condition":"11111","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":337014,"subject":"ZQ9M2","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43582","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cb8"},"rt":8325,"condition":"11111","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":345449,"subject":"ZQ9M2","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43582","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cb9"},"rt":7219,"condition":"11111","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":352800,"subject":"ZQ9M2","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43582","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cba"},"rt":38328,"condition":"11111","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":391251,"subject":"ZQ9M2","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43582","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"M X X O H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cbb"},"rt":78001,"condition":"11111","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":469358,"subject":"ZQ9M2","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43582","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cbc"},"rt":34773,"condition":"11111","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":504555,"subject":"ZQ9M2","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43582","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cce"},"rt":11922,"condition":"11111","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":35767,"subject":"9P8T0","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42358","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88ccf"},"rt":11924,"condition":"11111","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":48166,"subject":"9P8T0","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42358","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"2C F F B B E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cd0"},"rt":12652,"condition":"11111","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":60922,"subject":"9P8T0","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42358","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,U,B","hovered":"A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cd1"},"rt":26553,"condition":"11111","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":88233,"subject":"9P8T0","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42358","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"C 01 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cd2"},"rt":19204,"condition":"11111","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":107683,"subject":"9P8T0","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42358","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"F O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cd4"},"rt":16850,"condition":"11111","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":131868,"subject":"9P8T0","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42358","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cd5"},"rt":27410,"condition":"11111","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":159400,"subject":"9P8T0","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42358","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"6B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cd6"},"rt":23368,"condition":"11111","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":182868,"subject":"9P8T0","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42358","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"8C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cd7"},"rt":3136,"condition":"11111","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":186100,"subject":"9P8T0","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42358","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cd8"},"rt":1301,"condition":"11111","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":187500,"subject":"9P8T0","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42358","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cd9"},"rt":1706,"condition":"11111","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":189350,"subject":"9P8T0","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42358","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cda"},"rt":1806,"condition":"11111","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":191251,"subject":"9P8T0","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42358","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cdb"},"rt":1798,"condition":"11111","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":193149,"subject":"9P8T0","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42358","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cdc"},"rt":1841,"condition":"11111","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":195084,"subject":"9P8T0","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42358","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cdd"},"rt":1406,"condition":"11111","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":196584,"subject":"9P8T0","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42358","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cef"},"rt":53078,"condition":"11111","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":122544,"subject":"QLKDR","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44400","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cf0"},"rt":14055,"condition":"11111","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":136697,"subject":"QLKDR","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44400","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"H D K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cf1"},"rt":21116,"condition":"11111","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":157910,"subject":"QLKDR","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44400","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C C Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cf2"},"rt":8843,"condition":"11111","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":166846,"subject":"QLKDR","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44400","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cf3"},"rt":20857,"condition":"11111","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":187804,"subject":"QLKDR","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44400","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"H I O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cf5"},"rt":8661,"condition":"11111","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":202939,"subject":"QLKDR","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44400","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cf6"},"rt":25079,"condition":"11111","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":228111,"subject":"QLKDR","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44400","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"C O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cf7"},"rt":50851,"condition":"11111","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":279058,"subject":"QLKDR","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44400","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,G","hovered":"C B B B G G G F C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cf8"},"rt":116920,"condition":"11111","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":396076,"subject":"QLKDR","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44400","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"C C J J J J J J J B B I J J A A A J B B B M 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cf9"},"rt":20201,"condition":"11111","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":416562,"subject":"QLKDR","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44400","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F M J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cfa"},"rt":23851,"condition":"11111","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":440517,"subject":"QLKDR","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44400","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cfb"},"rt":12320,"condition":"11111","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":452928,"subject":"QLKDR","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44400","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cfc"},"rt":17095,"condition":"11111","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":470130,"subject":"QLKDR","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44400","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cfd"},"rt":7546,"condition":"11111","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":477768,"subject":"QLKDR","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44400","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88cfe"},"rt":15380,"condition":"11111","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":493246,"subject":"QLKDR","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44400","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"X 02 PM02 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d10"},"rt":26549,"condition":"11111","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":133255,"subject":"MXQDT","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40612","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"J O A C A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d11"},"rt":11104,"condition":"11111","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":144484,"subject":"MXQDT","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40612","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"K D E E E H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d12"},"rt":48947,"condition":"11111","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":193551,"subject":"MXQDT","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40612","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":11,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,X,O,I,J,H,F,K,D,U,E,G,B,Z","hovered":"F A C A F C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d13"},"rt":39425,"condition":"11111","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":233370,"subject":"MXQDT","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40612","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"05 PM04 PME "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d14"},"rt":12395,"condition":"11111","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":245894,"subject":"MXQDT","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40612","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I I O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d16"},"rt":58147,"condition":"11111","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":310745,"subject":"MXQDT","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40612","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,L,P","hovered":"X X N D 06 PM05 PM12 PM11 AMI 10 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PMH H L L L L H L P "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d17"},"rt":34629,"condition":"11111","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":345496,"subject":"MXQDT","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40612","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM10 AM09 AMI 10 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM02 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d18"},"rt":132161,"condition":"11111","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":477778,"subject":"MXQDT","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40612","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":"F B X X 11 AM10 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PMX 01 PM12 PMX 10 AM09 AMM B B B O O F B B O O C C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d19"},"rt":19023,"condition":"11111","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":497131,"subject":"MXQDT","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40612","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"J B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d1a"},"rt":10984,"condition":"11111","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":508240,"subject":"MXQDT","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40612","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d1b"},"rt":10619,"condition":"11111","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":518981,"subject":"MXQDT","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40612","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B B B B 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d1c"},"rt":22331,"condition":"11111","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":541437,"subject":"MXQDT","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40612","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d1d"},"rt":44622,"condition":"11111","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":586182,"subject":"MXQDT","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40612","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"I H H Z X X K O O X X 02 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d1e"},"rt":59822,"condition":"11111","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":646837,"subject":"MXQDT","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40612","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"X X M X 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d1f"},"rt":17402,"condition":"11111","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":664360,"subject":"MXQDT","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40612","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"M 01 PM02 PMX X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d31"},"rt":25535,"condition":"11111","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":97891,"subject":"ZLXTG","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38119","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"09 AM11 AMA 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d32"},"rt":115583,"condition":"11111","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":213579,"subject":"ZLXTG","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38119","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"D D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d33"},"rt":13135,"condition":"11111","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":227016,"subject":"ZLXTG","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38119","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d34"},"rt":117457,"condition":"11111","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":344580,"subject":"ZLXTG","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38119","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"09 AM03 PM04 PME E 01 PM02 PMU U U O 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d35"},"rt":91714,"condition":"11111","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":436603,"subject":"ZLXTG","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38119","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"Z O 03 PM03 PM11 AM11 AMO 03 PM03 PM04 PM03 PMH H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d37"},"rt":8007,"condition":"11111","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":451287,"subject":"ZLXTG","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38119","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d38"},"rt":21603,"condition":"11111","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":472994,"subject":"ZLXTG","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38119","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d39"},"rt":66354,"condition":"11111","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":539452,"subject":"ZLXTG","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38119","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E E E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d3a"},"rt":33961,"condition":"11111","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":573717,"subject":"ZLXTG","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38119","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I X X 12 PMB B B B 12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d3b"},"rt":41999,"condition":"11111","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":615825,"subject":"ZLXTG","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38119","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F F F B B 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d3c"},"rt":40315,"condition":"11111","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":656246,"subject":"ZLXTG","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38119","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"09 AM01 PM12 PM12 PMB B B B 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d3d"},"rt":8907,"condition":"11111","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":665263,"subject":"ZLXTG","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38119","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d3e"},"rt":28552,"condition":"11111","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":693920,"subject":"ZLXTG","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38119","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d3f"},"rt":25264,"condition":"11111","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":719291,"subject":"ZLXTG","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38119","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"J M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d40"},"rt":32606,"condition":"11111","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":752001,"subject":"ZLXTG","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38119","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"02 PMX X X 11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d52"},"rt":27255,"condition":"11111","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":78954,"subject":"FK4SQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36789","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"Z A A 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d53"},"rt":22074,"condition":"11111","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":101124,"subject":"FK4SQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36789","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"H D D D D 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d54"},"rt":13848,"condition":"11111","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":115070,"subject":"FK4SQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36789","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"A C C A Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d55"},"rt":62852,"condition":"11111","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":178006,"subject":"FK4SQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36789","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"A 03 PM04 PMU K H J J H H H H H H H J J F F F Z Z Z O O O O O O 7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d56"},"rt":106171,"condition":"11111","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":284453,"subject":"FK4SQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36789","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"I I 12 PM12 PM12 PM12 PM12 PM11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AMI I O 11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM02 PM04 PM03 PM05 PM04 PMU U U U K K K K K K K K K K K K K K 03 PM04 PM04 PMH H H H A A Z F F F F O O O O O O O H H H 01 PM02 PM02 PM03 PM04 PMH J U U K K K K K K 03 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d58"},"rt":15998,"condition":"11111","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":306454,"subject":"FK4SQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36789","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d59"},"rt":16875,"condition":"11111","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":323422,"subject":"FK4SQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36789","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F F B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d5a"},"rt":43862,"condition":"11111","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":367372,"subject":"FK4SQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36789","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"L G G J J X J I I I I B E E E E F J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d5b"},"rt":19658,"condition":"11111","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":387113,"subject":"FK4SQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36789","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d5c"},"rt":52686,"condition":"11111","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":439885,"subject":"FK4SQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36789","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"B F C F F B B 12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PMM 01 PM01 PMX X O O X 04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d5d"},"rt":5494,"condition":"11111","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":445466,"subject":"FK4SQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36789","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d5e"},"rt":6299,"condition":"11111","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":451851,"subject":"FK4SQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36789","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d5f"},"rt":15390,"condition":"11111","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":467335,"subject":"FK4SQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36789","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"X Z Z Z O F F F F F M X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d60"},"rt":48105,"condition":"11111","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":515527,"subject":"FK4SQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36789","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"02 PM04 PM03 PM03 PM303 PM04 PM03 PM03 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d61"},"rt":37515,"condition":"11111","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":553128,"subject":"FK4SQ","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36789","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"X X M 02 PMX X X B B F B 11 AM09 AM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d73"},"rt":27633,"condition":"11111","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":152211,"subject":"WO711","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39710","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"1C Z 12 PM11 AMA A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d74"},"rt":13830,"condition":"11111","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":166138,"subject":"WO711","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39710","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"3E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d75"},"rt":23824,"condition":"11111","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":190054,"subject":"WO711","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39710","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C C 11 AMZ Z O O 12 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d76"},"rt":57335,"condition":"11111","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":247480,"subject":"WO711","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39710","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"Z K K K U U H J H H 3O H F F I O O O I I I O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d77"},"rt":39280,"condition":"11111","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":286857,"subject":"WO711","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39710","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I O O Z I I 11 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM01 PM03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d79"},"rt":7766,"condition":"11111","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":300013,"subject":"WO711","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39710","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d7a"},"rt":20941,"condition":"11111","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":321047,"subject":"WO711","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39710","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B B F F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d7b"},"rt":54629,"condition":"11111","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":375768,"subject":"WO711","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39710","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F B B F F E J J J 11 AM12 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d7c"},"rt":24176,"condition":"11111","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":400047,"subject":"WO711","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39710","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d7d"},"rt":55998,"condition":"11111","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":456137,"subject":"WO711","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39710","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F B M C I E E E F F F E E E 12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM04 PMO F B 12 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d7e"},"rt":22268,"condition":"11111","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":478496,"subject":"WO711","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39710","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"7B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d7f"},"rt":23648,"condition":"11111","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":502240,"subject":"WO711","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39710","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d80"},"rt":70383,"condition":"11111","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":572726,"subject":"WO711","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39710","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"Z C C C X 04 PMZ Z O L H Z G G G G G F F E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d81"},"rt":84262,"condition":"11111","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":657244,"subject":"WO711","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39710","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"03 PMI J J J E C E B B F B B 01 PM02 PMJ J C G G C C X 02 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d82"},"rt":52764,"condition":"11111","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":710279,"subject":"WO711","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39710","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"02 PM10 AMI I I 10 AMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d94"},"rt":65546,"condition":"11111","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":193831,"subject":"L1NUX","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44459","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"C 09 AM09 AM09 AM08 AM09 AM09 AM08 AMC C 10 AM11 AMA A A A 08 AMA A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d95"},"rt":59019,"condition":"11111","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":253612,"subject":"L1NUX","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44459","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"D E E U 01 PM02 PMZ Z D D E K D E E 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d96"},"rt":126871,"condition":"11111","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":380708,"subject":"L1NUX","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44459","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"C C C D K O 1008 AM08 AMI 10 AMC C C C C C X I D K 03 PMK K K K K K U 03 PM02 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM08 AM08 AMI I X 08 AMC C 10 AM10 AMC C O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d97"},"rt":38494,"condition":"11111","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":419938,"subject":"L1NUX","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44459","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,U","hovered":"C 01 PM01 PM03 PM04 PM04 PME E 04 PM04 PME E E E D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d98"},"rt":397770,"condition":"11111","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":817934,"subject":"L1NUX","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44459","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"O O I X I I O I I I X X X U 02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM01 PM01 PM12 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d9a"},"rt":110072,"condition":"11111","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":940722,"subject":"L1NUX","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44459","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"12 PMM E E E G G E G G I E E G G E 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d9b"},"rt":37410,"condition":"11111","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":978994,"subject":"L1NUX","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44459","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"C H C C F F F I J B B M O Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d9c"},"rt":229833,"condition":"11111","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1209049,"subject":"L1NUX","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44459","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"L G E G F F B B F F F F B B 12 PME E B X X X X X X X X X E K K X X X X K K X X X X X L L G E E E J 12 PMX E 11 AME M X 02 PM04 PM04 PM04 PME I J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d9d"},"rt":28846,"condition":"11111","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1238620,"subject":"L1NUX","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44459","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"G D J J I B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d9e"},"rt":67809,"condition":"11111","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1306643,"subject":"L1NUX","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44459","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F Z Z Z 04 PMZ Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88d9f"},"rt":20471,"condition":"11111","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1327980,"subject":"L1NUX","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44459","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"01 PM12 PMB B B 12 PMB B F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88da0"},"rt":16327,"condition":"11111","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1344469,"subject":"L1NUX","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44459","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F F F F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88da1"},"rt":53957,"condition":"11111","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1398685,"subject":"L1NUX","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44459","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"E Z Z Z Z Z Z B O O Z Z I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88da2"},"rt":21823,"condition":"11111","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1420728,"subject":"L1NUX","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44459","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"46"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88da3"},"rt":161963,"condition":"11111","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1582910,"subject":"L1NUX","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44459","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"X F F 01 PM02 PM02 PM02 PMX X X X X X X 02 PMX X X 02 PMX 02 PMX X 11 AMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88db5"},"rt":21131,"condition":"11111","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":225737,"subject":"C4F6K","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44454","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"309 AM10 AM11 AMA A A C A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88db6"},"rt":13432,"condition":"11111","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":239260,"subject":"C4F6K","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44454","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"J D D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88db7"},"rt":17560,"condition":"11111","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":256908,"subject":"C4F6K","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44454","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"5O O O C C A A Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88db8"},"rt":73605,"condition":"11111","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":330612,"subject":"C4F6K","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44454","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"F U U 404 PMO K 05 PM04 PM05 PM04 PMO K E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88db9"},"rt":137178,"condition":"11111","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":468095,"subject":"C4F6K","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44454","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"08 PM07 PMI 11 AMF 12 PMZ Z I I I O O I F F I I 03 PMA C A U U 03 PMU H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88dbb"},"rt":10853,"condition":"11111","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":493019,"subject":"C4F6K","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44454","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"66"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88dbc"},"rt":30432,"condition":"11111","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":523543,"subject":"C4F6K","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44454","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F B B 4C C H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88dbd"},"rt":60340,"condition":"11111","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":583982,"subject":"C4F6K","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44454","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"5B B B Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88dbe"},"rt":42653,"condition":"11111","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":626941,"subject":"C4F6K","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44454","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"O B B B B J B B I B B B 1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88dbf"},"rt":51565,"condition":"11111","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":678599,"subject":"C4F6K","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44454","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,X","hovered":"B O C F Z Z Z G H B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88dc0"},"rt":9169,"condition":"11111","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":687868,"subject":"C4F6K","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44454","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"44J 02 PM01 PM12 PMB B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88dc1"},"rt":14298,"condition":"11111","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":702269,"subject":"C4F6K","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44454","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B O M J N B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88dc2"},"rt":26167,"condition":"11111","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":728527,"subject":"C4F6K","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44454","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"04 PMZ Z Z Z Z Z Z Z Z Z Z Z Z Z Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88dc3"},"rt":36054,"condition":"11111","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":764675,"subject":"C4F6K","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44454","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"H 03 PMO O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88dc4"},"rt":44579,"condition":"11111","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":809348,"subject":"C4F6K","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44454","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"I 03 PM02 PMX X X X F C K K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88dd6"},"rt":93628,"condition":"11111","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":229211,"subject":"D3S8F","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35855","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"X X 02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM08 AM08 AM09 AM10 AM10 AM12 PMA A A A A A A Z 12 PM11 AMA A 10 AMF F F 11 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PMA A A 10 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM11 AMG U 02 PM03 PMZ 03 PM03 PM11 AM10 AMA A 11 AM02 PM01 PM11 AM11 AM11 AM10 AM09 AM09 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88dd7"},"rt":20800,"condition":"11111","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":250294,"subject":"D3S8F","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35855","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"3K Z D D K K 101 PME E D D D K K K K 12 PMD K 08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88dd8"},"rt":13252,"condition":"11111","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":263643,"subject":"D3S8F","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35855","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AM08 AM09 AMC F F F A C C C 10 AM11 AMC A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88dd9"},"rt":15172,"condition":"11111","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":278918,"subject":"D3S8F","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35855","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"Z 04 PM05 PM05 PM04 PM603 PM04 PM05 PM04 PM03 PM04 PMH A H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88dda"},"rt":41096,"condition":"11111","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":320152,"subject":"D3S8F","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35855","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"7I I I I O O F F F F F F I I I I I O O O I O O F F F F F F I I F F F F F F F I U U I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88ddc"},"rt":10132,"condition":"11111","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":335550,"subject":"D3S8F","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35855","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"J 09 AME 666E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88ddd"},"rt":47008,"condition":"11111","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":382698,"subject":"D3S8F","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35855","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"F 01 PMJ I 01 PM02 PM01 PM09 AM10 AMB F F B B B B B C 01 PMN H O O X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88dde"},"rt":75091,"condition":"11111","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":457907,"subject":"D3S8F","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35855","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,G","hovered":"B X C G G G E E G G E 02 PME E G C O O 04 PMG G C C G G G C C C H H C C C X M 04 PM12 PMF F C C C G C C C O 04 PM03 PM04 PMC G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88ddf"},"rt":23244,"condition":"11111","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":481425,"subject":"D3S8F","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35855","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J B B 09 AM10 AM1009 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88de0"},"rt":6341,"condition":"11111","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":487869,"subject":"D3S8F","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35855","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"01 PM03 PMF 02 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88de1"},"rt":10335,"condition":"11111","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":498299,"subject":"D3S8F","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35855","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M L L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88de2"},"rt":7703,"condition":"11111","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":506094,"subject":"D3S8F","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35855","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B G G 5G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88de3"},"rt":12953,"condition":"11111","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":519142,"subject":"D3S8F","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35855","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"E G A O Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88de4"},"rt":6875,"condition":"11111","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":526111,"subject":"D3S8F","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35855","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"110 AM11 AM04 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83aa70a7aae4618c88de5"},"rt":45138,"condition":"11111","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":571350,"subject":"D3S8F","study":"SGC5A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35855","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"12 PM01 PM02 PMX X X X X X B G 02 PM02 PMX X "}]
